popularcommunitybank.com 2019-05-17

# Popular Privacy Policy

                                                                                                                                           Rev. 04/18
Popular Privacy Policy
                         WHAT DOES POPULAR, INC.
      FACTS              DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 Why?                    Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to
                         limit some but not all the information that can be shared. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect,
                         share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
 What?                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.
                         This information can include:
                         • Social Security number and income
                         • Account balance and transaction history
                         • Payment history and credit history
 How?                    All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the
                         section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the
                         reasons Popular, Inc. chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
 Reasons we can share your personal information                                      Does Popular, Inc. share?        Can you limit this sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes—such as to process your transactions,                         Yes                               No
 maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations,
 or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes—to offer our products and services to you                             Yes                               No
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                               Yes                               No
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your                            Yes                               No
 transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your                            Yes                              Yes
 creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                                              Yes                              Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                               No                        We don’t share
 To limit                Mail the form below.
 our sharing             Please note:
                         If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 45 days from the date we sent this notice.
                         When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
                         However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
 Questions?              Call toll-free: 1.888.610.5925
 Mail-in Form                   NO ACTION IS REQUIRED if you previously chose to opt-out of sharing your information.
 If you have a joint            Mark any/all you want to limit:
 account, your choice(s)        ___Do not share information about my creditworthiness with your affiliates for their everyday business purposes.
 will apply to everyone         ___Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me.
 on your account unless
 you mark below.                Name
 ___Apply my choice(s)          Address
 only to me.
                                City, State, Zip
                                Account No(s)
 Mail To:                       Popular, Inc.
                                Ops Compliance Unit (PB 5-5)
                                P.O. Box 5490
                                Miami Lakes, FL 33014-8500

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?          Popular, Inc. and its affiliates (see definition below)
What we do
How does Popular, Inc. protect         To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security
my personal information?               measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and
                                       secured files and buildings. Also, we limit the access only to employees who need it to provide
                                       products and services, or to comply with federal and local regulations.
How does Popular, Inc. collect         We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
my personal information?               • Open an account or show your driver’s license
                                       • Apply for a loan or show your government issued ID
                                       • Provide employment information or provide account information
                                       We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or
                                       other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?         Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                       • Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
                                       • Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                       • Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                       State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
                                       (See below for more on your rights under state law.)
What happens when I limit sharing      Your choice(s) will apply to everyone on your account—unless you tell us otherwise.
for an account I hold jointly with
someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                             Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial
                                       companies.
                                       • Our affiliates include companies with Popular, Inc; financial companies such as Popular Bank,
                                          Popular Equipment Finance, Popular Insurance Agency USA, Banco Popular de Puerto Rico,
                                          and E-Loan, Inc.
Nonaffiliates                          Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                       nonfinancial companies.
                                       • Popular, Inc. does not share with nonaffiliates.
Joint marketing                        A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial
                                       products or services to you.
                                       • Our joint marketing partners include: direct marketing, insurance companies, financial service
                                          companies, investment securities and/or brokerage firms.
Other important information
California Residents – Your state law requires financial institutions to obtain your consent prior to sharing information about you with
nonaffiliated parties. Except as permitted by law, we will not share information we collect about you with nonaffiliated third parties
while you are a resident of California.
Vermont Residents – We do not share information we collect about you with nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by
Vermont law, such as to process your transactions or maintain your account. In addition, we will not share information about your
creditworthiness with our affiliates, except with your authorization.
Nevada Residents – Pursuant to Nevada law, if you prefer not to receive marketing calls from us, you may be placed on our internal
Do Not Call list by writing to us at: Popular, Inc., P.O. Box 5490, Miami Lakes, FL 33014-8500.
For more information, contact us at the address above. You may also contact the Nevada Attorney General’s Office at:
Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101;
telephone number: 702.486.3132; online: http://ag.nv.gov/
